The trap is set.
Entrapment is a romance, drama, mystery film directed by Jon Amiel.
Two thieves, who travel in elegant circles, try to outsmart each
other and, in the process, end up falling in love.
Virginia "Gin" Baker, played by Catherine Zeta-Jones.
Robert "Mac" MacDougal, played by Sean Connery.
Hector Cruz, played by Will Patton.
Conrad Greene, played by Maury Chaykin.
Aaron Thibadeaux, played by Ving Rhames.
Haas, played by Kevin McNally.
Entrapment is a 1999 heist film directed by Jon
Amiel and written by Ronald Bass.
It stars Sean Connery and Catherine Zeta-Jones and includes
Will Patton, Ving Rhames and Maury Chaykin.
The film focuses on the relationship between an investigator and a professional
thief as they attempt a heist at the turn of the millennium.
Simon West and Antoine Fuqua were both in talks
to direct before Amiel was hired.
Principal photography took place from June to October
1998 at locations in Britain and Malaysia.
The score was composed by Christopher Young, and British singer
Seal performs "Lost My Faith" over the end credits.
Entrapment was released theatrically in the United States on 30
April 1999 and in the United Kingdom on 2 July.
It received mixed reviews from critics, and grossed $212 million
worldwide on a $66 million production budget.
The film explores themes of new year's eve, london,
england, distrust, undercover, burglar.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.